I'm getting my nails done!
我居然在修指甲
You said it was going to be fun.
你说会很好玩
Which it kind of is.
是有点好玩
You said there would be guys. There are no guys.
你说会有别的男人，哪有啊
There's one right over there.
那边就有一个
That's a mailman!
那是快递
That's our mailman!
他也跑我们公司
Hi,how are you....
Don't worry. This doesn't make you any less of a guy.
放心 这样无损于你的男子气概
That does.
那样会
What am I sitting on?
我坐到什么？
What was this woman scratching when this broke off?
这个女人不知道在搔哪里
You know who had nails like that?
你知道谁也戴那种指甲？
Oh...
我…
...my...
的…
...God!
天哪！
The One with All the Rugby
本集播出：“调职记”
rainystar压制iPod-MP4
Joey,let me ask you a question.
乔伊，问你一个问题
What does this light switch do?
我快捉狂了 这个开关是干嘛用的？
Nothing.
没用
Did it drive you crazy to not know?
你不知道不会捉狂吗？
I know what it did. Nothing.
我知道啊. 它没用
They put it there for something. How can you not care?
它存在就一定有功用 你怎么能不在意？
Like this.
就像这样
Here's another question.
还有一个问题
What does the silver knob on the toilet do?
你知道马桶上的把手的功用吗
It flushes it.
当然知道，冲水
Since you know,when you come over, would you use it?
很好，既然你知道，来的时候 请你冲一下好吗？
-Hello. -Hey.
-Oh,my God. Wow. -Guess who we saw today?
猜我们今天遇见谁
-Janice! -ls this amazing?
珍妮丝 很棒吧？
-How have you been? -Well,I'm divorced.
你好吗？ 我离婚了
Oh,wow.
I'm riding the alimony pony.
正在靠赡养费过活
And there it is.
出现了
I just came up to say "hi."
我只是来打声招呼，大家好
Sweetie,I'll see you later.
亲爱的，我们待会见
I'll see you tonight.
晚上见
-Bye. -Bye.
再见，再见…
I can't stand the woman!
我受不了那个女人
What? I thought you were crazy about her!
什么？我以为你爱死她了
But you know all those annoying things she did before?
我知道 但是以前她那些很烦的特点
Her voice,her laugh and her personality?
她的声音、笑声和个性
They're all back!
全都回来了
And she's picked up,like, nine new ones!
而且还多了起码九种新的
Why'd you bring her here? There's people here!
那你干嘛带她来？虐待人嘛
Don't worry. I'm taking care of it.
放心，我今晚会搞定
You are not! You never break up with her.
会才怪，你一直跟她纠缠不清
I don't have to break up.
这次我不必跟她分手
We're not involved. I'll do a preemptive strike.
我们又没在一起 我会先发制人
I'll end it with her before it starts.
我会在开始前就结束掉
My ass is,like,frozen!
我的屁股好冰
Try sticking it in the freezer for 20 minutes.
塞进冷冻库20分钟试试看
I'm telling you!
不要不信
I can't believe you walk alone here at night.
你居然敢晚上自己走在路上
-You hear such stories about New York. -It's not that bad.
纽约的传闻好多 没那么严重
I mean,l,for one, feel perfectly safe.
我就觉得很安全
Help! Help!
救命啊！救命啊！
No,no,Ross!
罗斯，没事
These are friends from home.
他们是我在英国的朋友
Liam,Devon,this is Ross.
连恩，戴文，这是罗斯
-Hi,mate. -How are you,man?
老兄 你们好
That was a good one,huh? "Help! Help!"
我装得不错吧？ “救命啊！救命啊”
How are you?
你们好吗？
I've been meaning to ring you ever since I arrived...
我从一来就想找你们
...but I've been rather busy.
但是…我挺忙的
We have not seen each other since that U2 concert.
我们从U2演唱会之后 就没见过
Oh,my God. You're right.
天哪，没错
Actually,the last time we saw each other was the next morning.
应该说是演唱会第二天早上
Oh,Liam!
连恩
Oh,Liam.
So were you guys playing soccer?
你们在打足球？
Or should I call it "football"?
还是要说“踢”足球？
We were playing rugby.
我们在打橄榄球
In fact,we're playing tomorrow. You're welcome to play.
明天就有球赛，欢迎你参加
Ross play rugby? I don't think so.
罗斯打橄榄球？不要吧
What's so funny?
有什么可笑的？
Well,you're American,to start with. You don't have rugby here.
你是美国人 美国没有橄榄球
Well,we didn't have freedom here until 1776 either,so....
我们也是到了1776年 才独立自由
So,good! We'll see you at the park at two.
那好，明天2点公园见
Cheers!
干杯
Oh,boy! I just love to sing.
天哪，我最喜欢唱歌了
Yes,I know you do.
我知道你喜欢
The reason people complained...
其他人之所以抱怨
...was because they paid to hear the actor sing "Old Man River."
是因为他们是花钱听演员唱
Look at us!
你看看我们
Who would've thought Cupid had a station at 14th Street Nails?
想不到在美容院也有爱神驻扎
Okay,we have to talk.
我们得谈一谈
I'm just getting out of a very serious relationship.
我刚结束一段很认真的恋情
I know. And I'm just getting out of a marriage.
我知道，而我刚结束一段婚姻
Talk about "meant to be."
这就叫做三生注定
Right. But I think this is happening too soon.
对，但我觉得进展太快了
Oh,too soon,too schmoon!
什么太快，是太慢
Face it,I'm not letting you get away this time.
认命吧，这次我不会放过你的
I hear you!
我听见了
But...
但是
...unfortunately...
很不幸的
...my company...
我的公司
...is transferring me overseas.
要把我调到海外
Oh,no!
不会吧
Where to?
调去哪里？
To Paris?
巴黎？
No,not Paris.
不，不是巴黎
To London? Rome? Vienna?
伦敦？罗马？维也纳？
Barcelona?
巴塞隆纳？
Could you just stop talking for a second?
你先别讲话好吗？
Yemen.
叶门
That's right. Yes! I'm being transferred to Yemen!
对，没错，我要被调去叶门
When?
什么时候？
I don't know exactly.
我不太清楚
Well,I will just have to soak up every ounce...
那我只好细细品尝
...of Chandler Bing until that moment comes.
钱德宾的一切 直到那一刻来临
But I do know it's sometime tomorrow.
但我知道是明天某时
-Done? -Yep!
好了？ 对
What's up?
干什么？
This switch is driving me crazy.
这个开关快把我逼疯了
I turned it off and checked every outlet.
所以我把它关掉 检查每个插座
Four don't work,which means one is controlled by the switch.
有四个不能用 表示其中一个由它控制
So I plugged things in the outlets that make noise.
所以我插上会发出声音的东西
That way,when I turn it on, I just follow the noise.
到时候一打开 顺着声音去找就行了
Bet I stopped listening first.
我一定会第一个放弃
You know,you also could have used lamps...
你可以插电灯
...and followed the light.
然后找灯光
Yeah,well,I'm using noise.
我要找声音
So,everybody ready?
准备好了吗？
Here we go!
开咯
Something. I hear something. Where is it?
有声音，我听到了，在哪里？
It's coming from Joey!
是乔伊发出来的
Oh,my God! That's so freaky! Turn him off!
天哪，好诡异喔，把他关掉！
Could we put on the news? It might be raining.
可以看新闻吗？可能在下雨
Hold on. I'm watching this rugby thing on ESPN.
等一下 我在看ESPN的橄榄球赛
I'm man enough to play this sport!
了不起啊，我也能打
You're not even man enough to get the channel that carries the sport.
你家连运动台都没有
Hey there,Ross!
罗斯
Janice.
是珍妮丝
You know,you really didn't have to help me pack.
你真的不必帮我打包
When you said all you'd be doing before you leave is packing...
你说你出发之前都要打包
...you really didn't leave me much choice.
我还有什么选择
I thought I did, but I guess I did not.
我以为有，看来是没有
What's going on?
怎么回事？
I'm packing,you know, because I'm moving to Yemen tomorrow.
我要打包 因为我明天要搬去叶门
Thanks for telling me!
谢谢你告诉我啊
I'm going to be pretend-moving to Yemen. To get rid of her.
我是假装要搬去叶门 好摆脱她
Good one!
漂亮
Yemen! That actually sounds like a real country!
叶门，听起来还真像个国家
I'll show you how to roll your underwear and stuff it in your shoes.
钱德，快来 我教你怎么把内衣裤塞进鞋子
It's a space-saver.
可以省空间
I do that because it makes me look taller.
我那样做是想垫高
Come on!
钱德，来啊 好
-Joey,trade lives with me. -Nope.
乔伊，跟我交换人生 不要
Ross,I can't believe you said you'd play.
天哪，你看看 罗斯，你居然说你要打
This is brutal!
这种运动好野蛮
I can handle it.
我可以应付
Please,Ross. You got hurt playing badminton with my dad.
拜托 你连跟我爸打羽毛球都会受伤
That's because your mom's dog kept looking at me.
那是因为你妈的狗一直看我
Look! Right here, it's called a "scrum."
好，你看，这个叫斗牛阵
It's like a huddle.
就像聚商
And is a hum like a scruddle?
那商斗就像聚牛阵吗？
Ross,they're going kill you!
罗斯，他们会宰了你
Why are you doing this,anyway?
你为什么要打？
You should've seen the guy she used to date.
你们应该看看她以前交往的人
He's like "Joe Rugby"!
他活像颗大橄榄球
You're kidding! And he plays rugby? That's funny!
不会吧，而他又打橄榄球？ 好好玩
Oh,I see. You did that.
我懂你的意思了
She thought the very idea of me playing rugby was hilarious.
总之她觉得我打橄榄球很好笑
So I'll show her how tough I really am.
所以我要证明我有多猛
I'm sorry. You are a tough guy.
对不起，你说得对，你是很猛
The toughest paleontologist I know.
你是我认识最猛的古生物学家
Ross can take care of himself. It's not like he's Chandler.
没问题啦，罗斯会照顾自己 他又不是钱德
Thanks.
谢了
Don't worry about me.
别替我担心
I'll just look energetic and stay away from the ball.
我会装得很有冲劲 跟球保持距离
I'll be that guy, right outside the circle.
我会学那个人站在外面
Maybe there was a dog looking at him.
也许有狗在看他
Stay away from that guy and that guy...
罗斯，别靠近那个人、那个人
...and that one. Dude,they're all huge!
和那个人 他们都好壮
They're no bigger than me.
又没比我壮
You're closer to you. So you look bigger to you from where you are.
你离你比较近 所以看你自己比较壮
I'm going to go say "hello."
我去跟他们打个招呼
I kind of liked it.
还蛮可爱的
I know what to do.
我知道了
I've got to go Red Ross.
我要变成赤面罗斯
You know,Red Ross?
赤面罗斯啊
Totally don't know.
完全给他不知道
That time we were in line for Dances With Wolves...
那次我们去看“与狼共舞”
...and that guy cut in front of us and I just lost it?
有人插队，我不是就捉狂了？
Screamed at him,turned all red!
破口大骂，脸都涨红了
Red Ross!
赤面罗斯啊
You'll see!
等着瞧
Liam,do me a favor.
连恩，帮个忙
Go easy on Ross. It's his first time.
对罗斯手下留情 他是第一次打
You don't say?
是吗？
Good luck,babe.
加油
Come on,get in here!
老弟，快进来
Come on!
快点
Come on,get in the bloody scrum!
罗斯，快进来争球
Ross,get in!
罗斯，进去
Joey!
乔伊
You're not going to believe it! Joshua came in today,and guess what?
说了你一定不信 约书亚今天来，你猜怎样？
He asked you out?
他约你？ 没有
But I showed him some cuff links, and I felt his pulse.
不过我给他看一些袖扣 结果摸到他的脉搏
Saucy!
卯死了
-What are these? -Electrical plans for the building.
这是什么？ 这栋楼的电路图
Okay,should I be scared?
我应该被吓到吗？
I know that switch does something. I got these from City Hall.
那个开关一定有作用 这是去市政府调的
I just paid $25 and waited for three hours.
只花了25元，排了3小时
Wow! If only more people knew!
可惜大家不知道
All right,do you understand any of this?
你看得懂吗？
No,I don't understand any of this electrical stuff.
我对水电的事一窍不通
All right,does this look like a switch?
这看起来像开关吗？
I don't know.
我不知道
-ls this wiring? -I don't know.
这是线路吗？ 我不知道
That looks like a bunny though.
不过这个像小白兔
“叶门航空”
You really didn't have to take me to the airport.
你实在不必送我来机场
Oh,please. Every moment is precious.
拜托，每分每秒都很珍贵
Besides,someone had to ride with your luggage.
况且总得有人帮你提行李
And your friends don't seem to care that you're leaving.
你朋友好像都不关心你要走了
We're not that close.
我们其实没那么要好
Okay. So I guess this is goodbye then.
好，那就再见了
Oh,no!
不
It's not goodbye. I'm not leaving till you get on that plane.
还没呢 你上了飞机我才要走
Okay. Well,I guess it's just "wait here" then.
好，那就“请在此等候”
I need a fake ticket to Yemen.
我要一张去叶门的假机票
One ticket?
一张去叶门的机票？ 不是
I just need a pretend ticket.
我只需要一张假机票
I'm sorry. I don't understand.
抱歉，我不懂
Okay,what would you give a kid to play with?
好，你会拿什么给小朋友玩？
Are you traveling with a child?
您有带小孩子？
No.
没有
She'll think I'm handing you a credit card.
她会以为我在拿信用卡给你
But what I'll really hand you is a library card.
其实我拿的是借书证
A ticket to Yemen is $2100, and we don't take library cards.
去叶门的机票是2100元 我们不收借书证
What's the matter? Is something wrong?
怎么了？有什么问题吗？
Do you have to stay?
你得留下来吗？
American Express?
美国运通卡？
I can't believe they're doing that! I told them to go easy on him!
他们怎么这样 我明明叫他们手下留情
No offense,but sometimes it's hard to understand you,with the accent.
我没有恶意 但有时你的口音很难懂
That's just halftime. There's more.
才上半场结束，还有下半场
Did you see me?
你们看到了吗？
I was pretty good. That is one fun game!
我挺强的 好过瘾的球赛
Do me a favor? Grab me some water?
帮个忙，帮我拿点水
Thanks!
谢谢
I think I'm dying. I really do.
我觉得我快死了，真的
Poor baby!
真可怜
Tell my son that I love him.
告诉我儿子我爱他
Excellent! Got to have some more fun!
太好了，我还要再打个过瘾
They are killing you.
罗斯，你快被整死了
That's not true.
乱讲
She's right. You have to stop!
她说得对，你不能再打了
No! I'm not stopping. I'm Red Ross!
不行，我是赤面罗斯
Dude,you go back out there, you'll be Dead Ross.
你再上场会变成屎面罗斯
I'm not quitting. I'm going to finish this game.
我绝不退场，我要打完
If you insist on it, at least let me help you.
好，如果你一定要打 至少让我帮忙
It's no place for a woman. Those guys will grab anything!
不行，这不是女人玩的 那些人什么都捉
That's not it. I just know a few things that can help you inflict pain.
我不是要上场 我只是知道怎样让别人受伤
I like that.
我喜欢 是吗？
Listen closely.
听好
Devon has got a weak ankle.
戴文的脚踝很弱
One swift kick and he'll back off.
踢一下就会倒
Bad ankle. Got it!
好，脚踝虚，了解
And that big bloke with the beard? He's got a trick hip.
那个留落腮胡的大个子 腰部毛病很多
And David over there, he doesn't wear a cup.
那边的大卫没穿护裆
I could use that. Trick hip,no cup. Okay!
蛮有用的，腰不好 没穿护裆，好
And Liam's got bad knees. Hit him right and he'll go down like a lamp.
连恩的膝盖不好 看准了一撞就倒
But Liam's on my team.
但是连恩跟我同队
-I don't care. Just get him! -Go and get him!
我不管，你去宰了他 好，宰了他
I am going back in!
我要回场上了
Red Ross! Yeah!
赤面罗斯
What are these?
这些是什么？
Just some pictures I made and hung up.
我画了一些画挂起来
I thought they'd brighten up the place. Don't they?
好让客厅看起来更漂亮 有用吧？
No,don't.
There's no hole there. I just really like that picture.
那里没有洞 我只是很喜欢那幅画
Oh,my God! Look at this!
天哪，你看看
But there is a wire there! It's connected to something!
但是那边有电线 一定连到某个地方
I don't care! The wires have come loose in your head!
我不管，你才是脑筋脱线了
If I could follow the wire, I'd find out what it did.
顺着电线就能找出它的功用
And did you?
那你找到了吗？
No.
没有
It disappears behind there.
到了地板上就断了
For a minute,I thought it went downstairs.
Say hello to Mrs. Catrokis.
跟凯卓奇斯太太打招呼
-Hello,darling. -Hello,Mrs. Catrokis.
妹妹你好 凯卓奇斯太太你好
Hey,Mrs. Catrokis,do you know Kenny?
凯卓奇斯太太，你认识肯尼吗
You have got to be kid Wow!
不会吧
Are you sure you don't want a doctor?
你真的不去看医生？
No,that'll just bring me down!
不要，那样我会直接挂掉
This was great! I was great! This was a great day!
太棒了 我太厉害了，今天真过瘾
I'm buying everyone coffee.
我请大家喝咖啡
Just grab my wallet. It's in my pocket.
帮我拿皮夹，在我的口袋里
No,not you.
不是你
Your eye's still popping out. I'll go get some ice.
你的眼睛还是突的 我去拿冰块
Ice,yeah! I'm so in the mood for ice.
好 冰块，我正想吃冰块
You were amazing out there.
你刚才好神勇
I kind of was,wasn't l?
还蛮神勇的吧？ 开玩笑
Oh,my God!
I made a man twice my size cry!
我让一个壮我两倍的人哭了
I haven't done that since I was four and I washed my dad's Porsche with rocks.
上一次是4岁 我用石头洗我爸的保时捷
You really enjoyed yourself, didn't you?
你真的打得很过瘾对不对？
Are you kidding? I hurt three huge men.
开玩笑，我干掉三个大块头
I gave a guy a bloody nose!
还让一个人流鼻血
I'm not proud of it...
这没什么好得意的
...but I really am!
不过…我真的好得意
And it's all because of you.
都是因为你
-Wonderful,amazing you. -I think you've got a concussion.
最棒最棒的你 我看你是脑震荡了
No,I'm serious. Thank you.
不，我是说真的，谢谢你
You're welcome.
不客气
I'm sorry. Did that hurt you?
对不起，会痛吗？
It's worth the pain.
痛也值得
You know what? It's not.
其实不值得
This is the final boarding call for flight 664 to Yemen.
最后一次呼叫前往叶门的旅客
Well,I guess I gotta go.
看来我该走了
My Bing-a-ling.
我的宾淇淋
I'll wait for you.
我会等你的
How long will you be gone?
你要去多久？
Well,just until we find an energy source to replace fuel.
直到找出可以替代石油的能源
I'll write you every day.
我会每天写信给你
15 Yemen Road,Yemen.
叶门叶门路15号
Okay. Goodbye.
好，再见
钱德，钱德
Janice! There you are! I had to have one last kiss.
珍妮丝，你在这里 我得跟你做最后吻别
And also,you said you'd leave after I got on the plane!
另外你也说我一上机你就要走
No. I want to see you take off.
不，我想看着你起飞
Well,then I guess I'm going to Yemen.
那我要去叶门罗
I'm going to Yemen!
我要去叶门了
When we get to Yemen, can I stay with you?
到了叶门，我可以住你家吗？
All right. The super couldn't figure out what it did.
好，管理员不知道它的作用
The $200-an-hour electrician couldn't figure out what it did.
1小时2百的电工 不晓得它的作用
I've had seven pretty serious shocks.
我被狠狠电到七次
I give up.
我放弃了
Thank God.
谢天谢地
I guess Joey was right.
看来乔伊说得对
It does nothing.
它没有用
See?
你看
I'm doing it! I am totally doing it!
是我弄的，真的是我弄的
I lost it.
超能力没了